{
    "subject": "Alan_Alda",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "War_of_Nerves__M*A*S*H_",
    "human_readable": "Alan Alda directed the episode War of Nerves from M*A*S*H.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9636003971099854,
            "question": "Was Alan Alda involved in directing episodes of M*A*S*H?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9541710615158081,
            "question": "Who directed the M*A*S*H episode 'War of Nerves'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9367268085479736,
            "question": "What is the name of the M*A*S*H episode directed by Alan Alda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.836887776851654,
            "question": "Did Alan Alda act in any episodes he also directed for M*A*S*H?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7859522104263306,
            "question": "Is Alan Alda known for directing other television shows besides M*A*S*H?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7415012717247009,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other role did Alan Alda have on M*A*S*H?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40416547656059265,
            "question": "What were the main characters' roles in M*A*S*H?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39670541882514954,
            "question": "What type of television show is M*A*S*H?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3301043212413788,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in M*A*S*H episodes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26807719469070435,
            "question": "In what decade did M*A*S*H air?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alan Alda directed the episode War of Nerves from M*A*S*H.",
            "html": "yago_26386_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in M*A*S*H episodes?",
            "html": "yago_26386_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of television show is M*A*S*H?",
            "html": "yago_26386_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the main characters' roles in M*A*S*H?",
            "html": "yago_26386_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26386_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the text, Alan Alda wrote and directed the episode \"War of Nerves\" from M*A*S*H (see file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26386/re-ranker-msmarco/44.txt and /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26386/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"War of Nerves\" was directed by Alan Alda, which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}